bestthemeswordpress.com 2012-09-19

# Privacy Policy | Best Themes 2012

The privacy and security of our site visitors is our highest priority. It is the policy of Premium WordPress that personal information, such as your name, personal postal and email address, or personal telephone number is private and confidential. Because your privacy is important to us, Premium WordPress maintains privacy policies to protect your personal information.

By using this site, you consent to the terms of our privacy policy for the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information for the purposes set out below. We do not collect, use or disclose your personal information for any purpose other than those identified below, except with your consent or as required by law.

Information we gather or track

(1) Site Activity Data  
Each time a visitor comes to this website, our web server collects and logs certain information. These access logs are kept for a reasonable period of time. These logs include, but are not restricted to your machine’s TCP/IP address, your username (if applicable), date, time and files accessed. These logs also contain information about ‘referrer’ information if you clicked on an external link to a Premium WordPress webpage. These logs are used solely for performance, site administration and security reviews. They are not sold or shared in any way to third party organizations.

(2) Cookies  
Your browser offers “cookies” which — if you allow their use — store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our site. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our offerings you like best. And when we make this function available in the future, cookies will enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. However, cookies tell us nothing about you personally unless you specifically give us additional information. This information is used solely to maintain your computer’s session to the Premium WordPress server. This information is not shared or sold to third party organizations for any purpose.

Some of the banner ads displayed on Premium WordPress are provided by outside companies. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our advertisers and we do not have access to this information.

Cookies in and of themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information about you.

(3) Personal Information  
Personal information, such as your name, personal postal and email address, or personal telephone number is collected only when you voluntarily provide it. Such information is received when you send an email through the site or make some other specific contact, such as completing an online form.

Policy Revisions  
Any changes to the privacy policy will be promptly communicated on this website. Policy changes will not alter how we handle previously submitted personal information.

Contacting BestthemesWordPress.Com  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact Premium WordPress at: support [at] bestthemeswordpress [dot] com
